

Jitesh Karania

Content & Copy Writer | Social Media Manager

A content writer, copywriter, and social media manager with two years of experience creating engaging content and managing social media for various clients. With a passion for storytelling and a deep understanding of the digital landscape, I have managed to specialize in crafting compelling narratives that resonate with target audiences and drive results. Whether it's writing blog posts and articles, or managing social media accounts. Looking to seek and maintain a fulltime position that offers professional challenges utilizing interpersonal skills, excellent time management, and problem-solving skills.

iteshwrk@gmail.com



+917709610808



💡 Mumbai, India



in linkedin.com/in/jitesh-karania

WORK EXPERIENCE

Content Development & Management (Consulting)

Working for clients like 6DegreesIT Pvt Ltd, Marker Content, Weaving Enterprises Pvt Ltd

01/2021 - Present

Responsibilities

- Researched, created, and edited blogs, articles, social media copies, and web pages for various brands
- Wrote original and engaging SEO content for digital marketing initiatives and brand communication

Content Creator

Entrepreneurial Ventures

Work

- Running a YouTube channel @UNHHgram with 110k subscribers & a food blog @thebhukkalife with 12.7k followers. Created content for different brands as a collaboration. Achieved these numbers organically.

Social Media Consultant

Ira Soilel by Amaltas Apparel and Accessories Pvt Ltd

08/2020 - 12/2021

Responsibilities

- Ideated, developed, and executed social media campaigns with the team
- Worked closely with the marketing team and the creative team. to develop and implement social media strategies and content

Internship

Gorewo (2022) & Success Forum (2019)

02/2022 - 05/2022

Responsibilities

- Developed strategies in content marketing for social media.
- Coordinated with a team of Graphic designers and Content writers for seamless execution.

Finance Executive

Intelenet Global Services Pvt Ltd

01/2017 - 05/2018

Achievements/Tasks

 Worked on Microsoft Excel for maintaining data and Outlook for coordination with clients on daily updates.

SKILLS

Copy and Content Writer

EDUCATIONS & CERTIFICATIONS

Bachelor of Commerce by Mumbai University

Social Media Marketing by HubSpot Academy

The Fundamentals of Digital Marketing by Google Digital Garage

Content Marketing by HupSpot Academy

Branding & Design by Sydney Romantics

Project Management by CBRE

Client Engagement by Bloomberg

National Stock Exchange's Certification in Financial Market

Diploma in Accounts & Finance by Finplan Institute of Management

VOLUNTEER

United Nations Volunteer

Raised awareness for causes of Air Pollution, Generation Equality & Covid 19 on Social media platforms. I have also been certified for my contribution.